<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
	<content contentuid="66523fb3deaa14de1766304e0911fbc49ae66" version="1">Artificer</content>
	<content contentuid="77523fb3deaa14de1766304e0911fbc49ae77" version="1">Masters of invention, artificers use ingenuity and magic to unlock extraordinary capabilities in objects.  They see magic as a complex system waiting to be decoded and then harnessed in their spells and inventions.  You can find everything you need to play one of these inventors in the next few sections.</content>
	
	<content contentuid="34523fb3deaa14de1766304e0911fbc49ae33" version="1">Alchemist</content>
	<content contentuid="45523fb3deaa14de1766304e0911fbc49ae44" version="1">An Alchemist is an expert at combining reagents to produce mystical effects.  Alchemists use their creations to give life and to leech it away.  Alchemy is the oldest of artificer traditions, and its versatility has long been valued during times of war and peace.</content>
	
	<content contentuid="36523fb3deaa14de1766304e0911fbc49ae33" version="1">Armorer</content>
	<content contentuid="47523fb3deaa14de1766304e0911fbc49ae44" version="1">An artificer who specializes as an Armorer modifies armor to function almost like a second skin.  The armor is enhanced to hone the artificer's magic, unleash potent attacks, and generate a formidable defense.  The artificer bonds with this armor, becoming one with it even as they experiment with it and refine its magical capabilities.</content>
	
	<content contentuid="38523fb3deaa14de1766304e0911fbc49ae33" version="1">Artillerist</content>
	<content contentuid="49523fb3deaa14de1766304e0911fbc49ae44" version="1">An Artillerist specializes in using magic to hurl energy, projectiles, and explosions on a battlefield.  This destructive power is valued by armies in the wars on many different worlds.  And when war passes, some members of this specialization seek to build a more peaceful world by using their powers to fight the resurgence of strife.</content>
	
	<content contentuid="33523fb3deaa14de1766304e0911fbc49ae33" version="1">Battle Smith</content>
	<content contentuid="44523fb3deaa14de1766304e0911fbc49ae44" version="1">Armies require protection, and someone has to put things back together if defenses fail. A combination of protector and medic, a Battle Smith is an expert at defending others and repairing both materiel and personnel.  To aid in their work, Battle Smiths are accompanied by a steel defender, a protective companion of their own creation.  Many soldiers tell stories of nearly dying before being saved by a Battle Smith and a steel defender.</content>
	<content contentuid="772d30149g1349g4008g9807g532569db7932" version="2">This companion's &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmourClass"&gt;Armour Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; and damage increase with the &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ProficiencyBonus"&gt;Proficiency Bonus&lt;/LSTag&gt; of its artificer.</content>
	
	<content contentuid="888f820e5gfdf7g4cc2g9309gb90acd0d2ff7" version="1">Steel Defender</content>
	<content contentuid="999f820e5gfdf7g4cc2g9309gb90acd0d2ff7" version="1">Your tinkering has borne you a faithful companion, a steel defender.  You can summon it freely and give it commands in battle</content>
    <content contentuid="77062bb49gc270g4353gb6ebgf4c2248ea879" version="1">Force-Empowered Rend</content>
	<content contentuid="77bf1636cgabfcg4312gbf40g99c410daea86" version="2">Lunge at a target to bite it</content>

	<content contentuid="88523fb3deaa14de1766304e0911fbc49ae88" version="1">Infusion Slots</content>
	<content contentuid="99523fb3deaa14de1766304e0911fbc49ae99" version="1">At 2nd level, you've gained the ability to imbue mundane items with certain magical infusions, turning those objects into magic items.</content>
	<content contentuid="11523fb3deaa14de1766304e0911fbc49ae11" version="1">Magical Tinkering</content>
	<content contentuid="22523fb3deaa14de1766304e0911fbc49ae22" version="1">At 1st level, you've learned how to invest a spark of magic into mundane objects. To use this ability, you must have thieves' tools or artisan's tools in hand.</content>

	<content contentuid="0e5ba292-48ab-4b1c-aa79-f25a635635a7" version="1">The Right Tool for the Job</content> Right Tool for the Job - Thieve's Tools - Display Name
	<content contentuid="ce18c051-d126-46dd-8447-8363b055f388" version="1">You've learned how to produce exactly the tool you need:  You can magically create thieves Tools, a trap disarmimg kit, or a shovel.</content> 
	<content contentuid="67f3c1eb-1289-42da-bf15-f72516588147" version="1">Craft: Thieves Tools</content> 
	<content contentuid="f3965b5b-adde-474a-b0ef-064552e3a491" version="1">Craft: Trap Disarm Kit</content> 
	<content contentuid="4a070d6a-fc4d-4a4a-b27d-5a00672af556" version="1">Craft: Shovel</content>
	<content contentuid="4893a0cc-7b69-47ab-9f1e-5480eb2f9f45" version="1">Infusions</content>
	<content contentuid="3a67dabd-e997-44ee-9c00-0a7e61628927" version="1">You've gained the ability to imbue mundane items with certain magical infusions, turning those objects into magic items.</content>
	<content contentuid="33d835bc-f003-4155-87a5-e4885eee5c90" version="1">Infusion: Enhanced Defense</content>
	<content contentuid="4513988f-89ea-4dde-a3b2-77de32ee9ecc" version="1">This infusion give a +1 bonus to Armor Class.  The bonus increases to +2 when you reach 10th level in this class.</content>
	<content contentuid="353ba4cc-52e7-4c22-aa6b-152f09fbbd84" version="1">Infusion: Enhanced Arcane Focus</content>
	<content contentuid="ba5ea8ae-f16a-4f8e-9170-e2825dfec9af" version="1">The target creature gains a +1 bonus to spell attack rolls and spell save DCs.  The bonus increases to +2 when you reach 10th level in this class.</content>
	<content contentuid="6f872d77-0743-41eb-a23c-59128e28b124" version="1">Infusion: Enhanced Weapon</content>
	<content contentuid="94cfcf4e-5099-45b1-87e6-8d1440727a34" version="1">The target weapon becomes magical and grants a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with it.  The bonus increases to +2 when you reach 10th level in this class.</content>
	<content contentuid="7bffca0d-2093-4911-97b9-ef5dbfc221a5" version="1">Infusion: Armor of Magical Strength</content>
	<content contentuid="e91f4da6-5297-4c7c-bd72-ca3dd2c4aa04" version="1">Infusion: Boots of the Winding Path</content>
	<content contentuid="52cb721b-dae9-40eb-ba8b-55ff8fcc19ea" version="1">Infusion: Helm of Awareness</content>
	<content contentuid="b27cabec-3fcb-424a-8557-c90330b28877" version="1">Infusion: Homunculus Servant</content>
	<content contentuid="d36daf64-1cf7-4c37-9bb2-99113afe8a1b" version="1">Infusion: Mind Sharpener</content>
	<content contentuid="c4672755-ea0e-4b0b-ba99-1f40f844b0ac" version="1">Infusion: Radiant Weapon</content>
	<content contentuid="df0307ba-33f3-4191-90c1-a56c4d717e00" version="1">Infusion: Repeating Shot</content>

	<content contentuid="777a55579g9844g4302g89e0ga6279822397b" version="1">Ring Mail Armour</content>
</contentList>